Hello to Ajay,
hello friends, health insurance
Guddu, I am Sumitra Bhandari, I
welcome you. Thank you very much
for watching this video. Today our topic
is best health insurance policy is not
possible. Who is the
best health insurance policy? The
concept of this is the only question due to which
we started the health insurance channel.
I am talking about big creatures.
When I started the health insurance work,
we started working by taking the policy of the company where I worked.
In the beginning itself, a very unfortunate accident happened. I had taken a
policy for one of my friends
and his child had an accident, then the
cashless rule would not come for three days. So
what is there, it is called that one your
training breaks down. There is a mixed realization
that when you are working, you
want things. When you are working in films,
you get hit by the ground reality.
And when I used to work, we used to do promotion in this company and
that company. Then I
took the agency of the same company and started working.
Today I do not work for this company.
My requirement at times is what is the
best health insurance policy for my clients.
So, over a period of time,
we have tied up with many companies in
different ways. So, today
after so many years, my experience is that it is not
possible to name the best health insurance policy in alphabetical order. Frankly speaking, we
cannot trust any company that it is the best health
insurance company. But when you
plan to buy a policy,
what does a normal consumer do? He meets with an
accident or he
just has money lying around or there is no
responsibility, so when he gets married, he
tells about some problem. He has also taken such a solid
cup of sugar. So, people become a little yagya
towards this net. I want a health
insurance policy. After that, what he does is that
he
asks some of his friends about buying a policy, then he
searches on Google. So, within a few days,
he may realize whether he
wants this thing or not. But the question is that he should get
5 lakh rupees for Pingla and some
companies do not have the top policy.  It is still late, it is
very cheap, so Giri Vrat, so leaving the real focus, they go and
answer that this
policy is very good, so the more people they
talk to, the one who got the claim under that policy, he will
study about it, the one who did
not get the claim, then he gets angry there, let me give you an
example, 15 years ago when it was the
era of credit, bad promises were made to people
and they were disillusioned, that is to say, there is no
credit card and
these things were misused and mis-sold, so
people did not know that there is a power,
so a lot of tigers were used, then they will
increase with that bank that friend, this is
very useless, the
intermediary who had given them that
credit card, his property is
also some of our problem, right, we did
not fulfill our duty, that we did not give proper understanding of that card,
because what happens is
that but when
this is not the only thing, then people
come on the basis of trust, a little bit of grade also works
that you get a very good thing, now the same thing
when you give it to someone else who  No,
when he searches for a policy, he asks a question to a friend
or whether he will get a positive reply or not
and there are very few people who have never had a
claim under health insurance,
this is 1995, so when he
searches on Google or
asks a friend, he gets a lot of
information, then information about new
products comes, that claim
settlement ratio, their purchasing
power, which is information, so that is
our mental state which a psychologist can judge,
now I can judge that hey, this
company is good and this one is bad, they
remain judgmental and have a complex system, it is
fun to say something very good, that this
company is bad, this company is very good,
I saw a video of a consumer of this company that it has become
useless, whereas when you are
buying a policy,
when you are buying a contract bike, you buy a
plot, a car, a mobile,
then it is your responsibility to read its specifications, its
terms and conditions,
how the property will be in your name,
while taking this insurance policy you
What is it that needs to be deleted?
People don't even pay one percent attention to that thing.
Unfortunately, 99% of them are having a
lot of fun with the challenge. They say, this
company is good or bad. This is nothing. I
say, today this company will be finished. This
single has a stand-alone policy. You
should take this risk. So what happened when I gained
knowledge, it also increases the fun. It
feels good to relax anyway. So
what happens is that we make a mistake.
We
don't give the conditions of our house. What is my help condition?
I know a lot of people, especially
in Bangalore, who are extremely ill.
People who are very ill and they have
even one percent feeling that they are ill. So,
we should not take this to our address. Look,
we did not look at our needs. You did not look at
incompatibility. You did not look at aspirations.
And you saw how my memory is before marriage.
How is it after marriage? After a female has a
child, are there any signs of help? So,
what happens? If these are so fast, then the
person gets such a mess that
We do not focus on our basic needs
and to find that policy, we do
interesting activities in the government to
find a good policy.
Policy sir, take any company's idea,
product is a product, these days understand this thing, the
99% of all the companies are the same,
you have an account in one bank, you have an account in another bank, the
ATM of one bank is dirty, there is
no good, you have withdrawn Rs
5,000, sir, you will withdraw Rs 5,000 and you will have to
give more money because a
distributed system is made, so
trust that system and focus on your need,
this was once a
big name of the company, if
you see today that company does not unite, then its
leg of 800 or LTE GSM was
taken over, now it will go positive, it will go negative,
Macromax is a company above, its corner has
changed, the name of the company is changing,
Religare Care's IPO has already happened,
okay, Star's IPO is about to come, okay,
Manish Pal Singh signed the first test
TTK was like this, so now you should carefully look at
what is basically going on in Reliance Health Insurance, standalone health insurance, in the last three years, our
industry is very dynamic, there will be a lot of changes in
your division, if
you focus on this thing, what do I need,
how much money can I offer, gradually,
how much Mahesh should be covered
and how much, according to my house,
what kind of policy should I take according to my budget,
some features I can opt for
and some features you should consider as necessary,
focus on this thing,
now let's face it,
we have to do a boring work in this, we have to
read the policy brochure and its
thirty-forty pages of terms and conditions,
now there is no excitement in this work, that if
this box will share some question, if there is any
problem, then it should be run on it, it should
not be like that you did this
and what was it, when you are doing this research yourself, it is a
cold Friday, it is a very good thing
but it is a very boring work,
most of the people write it down, it leads to decline, the
audience should read it, but what
This happens below, most of us
take responsibility for it, unless you have not read the
terms and conditions of any company,
you can accept this fact that if your
policy is 10-15 years old, there is a
possibility of some problem in changing it towards Vivo.
I will just remove this notion from your mind
that ICC is good, Bajaj
is good, New India Channel, ICC Champions, all the
companies do work worth crores of rupees at their place,
so check them,
what is our work, compare the policy terms and
conditions,
download and read the terms and conditions of three companies,
then you will know
what is the truth, it will take time, Meena, then
these legal documents of many things,
terms and conditions are
one sided contracts,
these terms and
conditions have not been made by asking 108 or asking me, whether you have read it
or not, it is not going to change,
but being the head of my family, if I have any
question, male or female, anyone
who has financial information within the family,
about these things.  I am
not saying that any madam will look after me,
you will have to enter into this policy, you will have to read the
terms and conditions,
some friend, friend, okay, friend,
any uncle told me this,
we have bought a plot there, take it brother,
but you, the CEO of your family, it is your
duty to grab the money of your family, wherever you are
investing money, do a little bit of your work on it,
so where you
should get free immediately very quickly, think that
this is a very good thing, very interesting, very
good offers are available, you need a little bit of pressure,
do your temptation that anything is
relative to the soldiers, its presentation is done like this, so
I am here against the
rules of defaming any company, for how many
years have you been working, till date I know
which is the best policy and the
best company, but after thinking I became an
insurance agent, I wanted to
work with any company, I am their
customer, you for me also, today this
third company which is 2025 company, it is
very difficult to find a good company among them, Roshni
Delhi  So you should not put it, sometimes the
CEO of a company is changing, sometimes
I was so angry with my daughter for that,
standardize the policy terms and conditions, the idea is so much messed up,
so now we
knew which one is the top ten and which one is the middle one
and which one is the bottom train, but what
happens is that despite that, it becomes very difficult to trust one hundred percent,
okay, right? Now this is a little true, it is a
bitter truth, people who get uncomfortable think
that man, he has
ended the story by taking one shot in one go, but see the truth is,
not everyone becomes successful by coming to any coaching center,
no child becomes a topper, look at your situation and
act according to your own, this is the right way,
okay, so the first thing is
that you should
remove from your mind the concept that
something happens by doing the best, okay, no one has
even got a car till date by doing the best, no such
mobile has come by doing the best, hey, the head keeps coming riding on a lion, the
situation in health insurance is very dynamic  Here the
submission matters how you use the Pulsar
bike and how much you have to mix
and how are you reviewing this policy in two-three years,
your city has
changed, your circumstances will change, there will be some
help condition, this is a dynamic journey,
so juice camera is not something like that,
do one thing and forget it, no, that is not possible,
I am India versus developing country, there are
many more notifications and I will tell you one small thing, if you are
sitting in a company, then what happens if
someone's name changes, then do not think of it as fate,
okay, your mind is audible, that if the
name of this company is changed, if this change happens, will
I leave from here, and in the meantime, if
you get an offer, then you will say, Sir, this
company is going to run away, this company is going to close,
please tell me in the midst of such rumours, if there is a
company on powder, a new company, a
person also wants to earn money, then no
one disturbs a good company, so I am
giving a big advice that if you
change the name of the company in a very simple way, then
you will have to worry  No worries, the ID is
there, have faith, wait, whenever you are a little
confused about development in America,
use confidence and try to raise your mind, then
some person will stick something or the other to you,
many times this happens in life,
you also have experience,
where we are sitting, we are
placed in a very good position in getting it made, so if you do
n't have the desire to jump around, then sit where you are sitting,
yes, in many places you are facing some
problem in this channel, if the policy seems weak, then you should
remove this thing, you will
get something with the best name, definitely subscribe to National Insurance Company, if there is nothing there, then
you should
definitely subscribe
and I want you to
join us, I am trying to make people aware,
yes this is the thing,
any policy, Gayatri, first
click on it for your new year 2019 and
when you come to any policy, then do not keep
sitting, the more you stay in one company, that
policy will become the best,
okay, so come and go to the website, you will get a
lot of claim settlement data
from their camera, do not get confused with it, detailed information from it  It is a bit
boring to spend too much time on the policy
terms and conditions, sit at home and
watch it, control your wife, your husband,
daughter,
stairs with your parents, what is the harm to people in the sports world, there can be
some technical thumb rule about how much poetry should be there, there are
benchmarks, you can add according to that too,
but if somewhere on YouTube, on
Google or on any website,
one or two three products are being promoted, then
understand that you are being saved from something there
or that person is a representative of a company,
I was here, that brother, sister, the
tree is wrong, it is not wrong to work to run your house, you should
sleep like you,
what do I need from this, that fish is not that, companies,
animal companies, government, private, do
not spend too much time in this,
for the box in your house, the more you
focus on your house, the
more simple and easy the policies will become for you, go on your mobile
internet, on Google, here you will do
your work at home, we want you,
within 1 hour, on this
topic,
we have ordered, any kind of information about my
video
Subscribe to our channel for knowledge, otherwise it is a
very good thing if you like this video, you do
n't like it, you can do it as per your
wish, the more simple
you will give a ticket, the more
you will get merit, the more it becomes easy for you,
my department wants that you should not suffer any loss, there should be
loss even in pursuit of more profit, so a very happy
Rakshabandhan to you
and try to make your day such that
you have such a skin, I
say that the best thing is that it is the same all the
days, so try to make your
health a party, after coming home with Aadhar number,
apply this turmeric and a half ten, if you
want to replace this oil, then you can gift it to a good friend,
brother-sister, someone to visit,
some help for exercise, some other bicycle, bicycle, you can get a bicycle,
its quality,
people here know that it is free
inside, see this, come on, it is fun, take
care of yourself and
if you like this video, then I have the feeling
of sharing it with your friends, I
say that it is
awesome, so take care of yourself,
this is going to come in a few minutes, make
yourself capable, take care of your health  Keep it and
install yourself, take it wherever you want,
but it's good to
check the seat first, you
took the time to watch this video, thank you
very much, thank you very much, stop it
[music]